<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ourkadai Technologies</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ourkadai Technologies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:02:50 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A1</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Who we are?
OurKadai Technologies is a consortium of steadfast, passionate &amp;amp; dedicated brains and minds, promoting the culture of Open-Source software. Our ethos is driven by the desire to contribute meaningfully to the technology and community through superior quality software solutions.
What do we do?
We design and develop web applications, integrate them seamlessly, automate business flows and enable cost-effective e-business solutions with alluring user experience through UI/UX.
Our Aim:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A1</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are digitally native and believe in being digitally ubiquitous Call Us @ (+91) 75984 00628
Mail Us @ operations@ourkadai.com
We fly high, yet we stay grounded Plot no.169, INTUC Colony,
Pethaniyapuram,
Madurai - 625016
Tamil Nadu, India</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A1</title>
      <link>/posts/articles/a1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/articles/a1/</guid>
      <description>I am a1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A1</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>Postgress Conference All You Need to Work with SQL is Just SQL Traditionally, we use Languages and Frameworks interact with Relational Databases. While these are effective in many ways, One problem is that, each of these brings new learning curve. It will be nice if we use SQL itself as the core skill and build application with plain simple SQL skills. In this webinar, I will demo this approach with a case study that builds simple, high performing Java application using Postgres database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A1</title>
      <link>/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/</guid>
      <description>MicroservicesIf you are looking for modernizing your legacy monolithic IT systems and applications into agile, small in size, messaging-enabled, autonomously developed, independently deployable, decentralized, and automated processes, converting each function as an individual service, then we are here to help you in making your microservices journey a painless, well-guided and successful one.
DevopsDevOps is not an end goal. It is a journey.Mere purchasing of DevOps tools doesn’t ensure you any success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A1</title>
      <link>/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/work/</guid>
      <description>Low Code/No Code Aurzart Made by musician for musician’ as the company slogan proudly pronounces, the whole ecommerce site is exclusively made, managed and operated day-in and day-out by a techno-novice music enthusiast, Martyn Charles, one of the early adopters of no-code platform. This techno-romance is empowered by Technology and OurKadai enabled this melodious technology rendezvous, a reality. We baby stepped a non-techie musician to the world of no-code platforms, without spilling any silvers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A2</title>
      <link>/posts/articles/a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/articles/a2/</guid>
      <description>I am a2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A3</title>
      <link>/posts/articles/a3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/articles/a3/</guid>
      <description>I am a3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Array</title>
      <link>/presentations/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/presentations/about/</guid>
      <description>Phase I - Inception (2010 - 2016)  The Problem Recruitment process based on below factors
Academic Score Tier 1 Colleges / City Communication Skills ( English )    logo copy Created with Sketch.                      Tech @ Park     Opportunity Meets Talent  Our Approach I</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ourkadai - Methodalogy</title>
      <link>/methodology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:02:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/methodology/</guid>
      <description>It’s no secret that Software (Industry) is changing. But gauging what changes are where the muddle starts. With 2 decades of rich experience in the industry and thoughtful observations, we believe the below are the few noteworthy changes that shape the industry. We focus on gearing up against these challenging facets.
 Technology is the Manager  Traditional 60%-40% mix of Technical &amp;amp; Non-Technical roles are no more relevant. 80%-20% mix is the order of the day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
